who blew hard b and through the bars of the pilot was silent at oases
用力吹b并穿过飞行员的栅栏的人对绿洲保持沉默
all the plantings are autobianchi seedlings
所有的种植都是autobianchi苗
so my these bolts are spring into life i can
所以我的这些螺栓如雨后春笋般涌现，我可以
it's time of the significance the mine train with the gregor's wide festivities
现在是具有格雷格庆祝活动意义重大的时刻了
at the times that open was the people of Madagascar
在开放的时代是马达加斯加的人民
you were with and sisters this is the and sisters
你和姐姐在一起，这是和姐妹们
your prevention cuddly doll it even my heating and family who and sisters how
您的预防措施可爱的娃娃甚至我的暖气和家人谁和姐妹如何
it's going to be a show b fine badge sweet party love and miserable existance
这将是一场表演b美好的徽章甜蜜的派对之爱和悲惨的存在
in the silents and it will arrange your return so they must therefore be blood out
在沉默中，它会安排你的返回，因此他们必须为此流血
and entertain with music and we dance [Music]
和音乐一起娱乐，我们跳舞[音乐]
the music was blue for it might be the the striker on the third
音乐是蓝色的，因为它可能是第三首
hester gray's temperley and die journey built vacation side
赫斯特·格雷的脾气暴躁和死亡之旅，打造度假胜地
and watch case themes that are gore with the music so that with me enjoy the
并观看与音乐相关的案例主题，以便与我一起欣赏
entertainment prepare for
娱乐准备
[Music] well
[音乐]好
debate is throwing one with sul grinding sheets or bread loves the great
辩论是用sul磨床或面包来爱一个伟大的人
[Music] I'm trying to get the game out of the moment
[音乐]我正在尝试暂时取消游戏
for partners it is boring and whether your knowledge and pace is a rolling table
对于合作伙伴而言，这很无聊，而您的知识和步伐是否是一个滚动表
the everyone thousand was karianne lively combination
每个人都是karianne活泼的组合
what do we have in a filius for ancestors or the de silents integrate
我们在祖先或德无言的融合中拥有什么
with their people if the chablis yes you are party
和他们的人在一起，如果夏布利，是的，你是聚会
and you easter of menno how that zoë of risky you how lives
你会在Menno的复活节中冒险吗？
taxis what is buddy maybe bread pack of models
出租车是什么哥们，也许是面包包的模型
distance to be placed in the family this is split-level casa
家庭中要放置的距离，这是错层式Casa
on joining if festival is the ceremony is an expansion of the
如果节日是仪式的话，那就是加入
musicians was pp flash show draw provider topic options
音乐家被pp Flash Show抽奖提供者主题选项
hermann maier new claims and the great deal or felt super pet too 4 so
赫尔曼·迈尔（Hermann Maier）的新主张和很多或觉得超级宠物也是如此4
his boat company and 2 ads so sink the dens of family
他的船公司和2条广告让家庭陷井
we offer many shade of white but this is one system that everyone ot had
我们提供许多白色的阴影，但这是每个人都拥有的一种系统
this is one with pride and anna too high bags rmn how much to shower
这是一个充满自豪和安娜过高的行李的人rmn要洗澡多少
will be praying spice and back home fit to shrug mountains for it is the
将祈祷香料和回到家适合耸耸肩膀的山，因为它是
fine let people lion a two and careful and maybe ancestors of god's wisdom
好吧，让人们狮子两个，并且是上帝智慧的祖先，也许是祖先
all fly time
所有飞行时间
[Music] and
[音乐]和